Guide to the George Leon Walker and Williston Walker Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Writings, Addresses, Sermons, Series IV
  - Williston Walker
    - Printed Essays and Addresses
      - Commemorative Address--Charles M. Lamson, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - Commemorative Address--George Barker Stevens, 1906 (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - "The Congregational Idea of Worship" (Hartford Seminary Record), 1894 (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - "The First Ecclesiastical Society in Hartford", 1903 (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - Historical Address--Tercentenary Anniversary of the Landing of the Pilgrims on Plymouth Rock, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - "The Influence of the Mathers in New England Development" (American Soc. of Church History), 1892 (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - "The Sandemanians of New England" (American Historical Association), 1901 (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - "Three Phases of New England Congregational Development" (Hartford Seminary Publication), 1893 (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - "The Validity of Congregational Ordination" (Dudleian Lecture), 1897 (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - "Why Did Not Massachusetts Have a Saybrook Platform" (Yale Review), 1892 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Others (received with Walker papers)
    - Leonard Bacon: A sermon preached at the induction of GLW into pastoral office in the First Church in Hartford, 1879 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - N. G. Clark: "Changes in the Usages of the Prudential Committee During the Last Ten Years", n.d. (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Elisha Williams: Sermon from Exodus 20:24, 1722 Feb. 16 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Payson Williston: Sermons, 1784-1803 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Payson Williston: Sermons, 1804-1833 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Unidentified: Essay re: Alexander Pope (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Essay directed to Board of Visitors of Andover Theological Seminary (Box 7, Folder 65)
- Notes, 1901-1902, n.d.; Series V
  - Notes in the handwriting of Williston Walker, primarily for lectures on church history, 1901-1902, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 67-71)
  - Notes in unidentified handwriting (Box 8, Folder 72)
- Personal Items and Memorabilia, 1890-1896; Series VI
  - Scrapbook of clippings relating to George Leon Walker and controversies at Andover Theological Seminary, 1890-1896 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Clippings relating to case of A. J. Covell of Andover before the A.B.C.F.M. (see also: Series III, Correspondence), 1887-1890, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Obituaries and other clippings relating to Connecticut Society of Colonial WArs, 1911-1913 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Copy of regulations for the election of alumni trustees; Amherst College, Association of Alumni, 1902 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Agreement between Williston Walker and publisher, Charles Scribner's Sons, 1893 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Genealogy of the Batelle Family (T.Ms.), n.d. (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Fragment of copy book with quotations from Revelations enverso, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Document relating to proposed plan of union of synod of New York and Philadelphia and the Consociated Churches in the Colony of Connecticut, c. 1766 (Box 9, Folder 77)